<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Kari Groszewska</title><link>https://karolinagroszewska.github.io/blogs/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Kari Groszewska</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://karolinagroszewska.github.io/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Helping Yourself</title><link>https://karolinagroszewska.github.io/blogs/workbalance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://karolinagroszewska.github.io/blogs/workbalance/</guid><description>Hello! It has been a really long time since I have gotten the chance to sit down and write a bit about my experiences. To be completely honest, I had the most difficult things in my life all coalesce together into one really excruciating period of time, and it took me a long time to recover.
Coming to you from right after winter break, I am here to provide some tips and tricks for surviving the tech world when it sometimes feels like you&amp;rsquo;re not welcome in it.</description></item><item><title>Resume Revamp</title><link>https://karolinagroszewska.github.io/blogs/resume-revamp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 10:44:38 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://karolinagroszewska.github.io/blogs/resume-revamp/</guid><description>My Qualms with Resumes Generally, I have always struggled with the idea of &amp;ldquo;selling myself&amp;rdquo; through a one-page PDF document in size 11 Times New Roman font. In high school I had a terrible time with college applications and supplements because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t bring myself to talk well about my accomplishments. They were things I was doing because I liked the other people I was working with, the type of work I was doing, rather than really talking about it.</description></item><item><title>How it came to be</title><link>https://karolinagroszewska.github.io/blogs/blog-intro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://karolinagroszewska.github.io/blogs/blog-intro/</guid><description>Hi! If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, you probably know who I am. If you don&amp;rsquo;t, well then you&amp;rsquo;re in a great place to learn and I would suggest hitting my name in the top left corner. That will give you at least a decent professional insight.
I tend to be pretty bubbly, so this blog is gonna do that justice. If that&amp;rsquo;s not your style, there&amp;rsquo;s plently of places elsewhere that I&amp;rsquo;m sure will hit a similar niche.</description></item></channel></rss>